<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<items>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginName</name>
		<heading>Name</heading>
		<description>Specifies the plugin name.&#10;&#10;Example: "Server restarter"</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginGuid</name>
		<heading>Guid</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the plugin's unique GUID, which serves as its identifier. It is a read-only value that is generated once during the plugin's creation and cannot be changed.</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginId</name>
		<heading>Id</heading>
		<description>This parameter specifies the plugin's ID, a read-only value that is generated once during plugin creation and cannot be changed. It is used to execute commands associated with a specific plugin when the same command exists in multiple plugins.</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginDescription</name>
		<heading>Description</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the plugin's description, providing details about its functionality and purpose.</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginType</name>
		<heading>Type</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the plugin type, indicating its category or functionality within the system. Possible values:&#10;&#10;
1. Monitoring
2. Alerting
4. Logging
5. Automation
6. Infrastructure
7. Configuration
8. Administration
9. Compliance and Audit
10. Other
		</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginAuthor</name>
		<heading>Author</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the author's name for the plugin, indicating who created or contributed to it.</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginVersion</name>
		<heading>Version</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the plugin's version, indicating its release number for tracking updates and compatibility.</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginWebSite</name>
		<heading>WebSite</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the author's website URL, providing a link to their official webpage or project site.</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginHelpShort</name>
		<heading>Help short</heading>
		<description>Specifies short plugin description. This value will be used to send to telegram chat when requested. Maximum length of the short description must be less or equal to 128 characters.&#10;&#10;Example: "Restarts specified server"</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginCommands</name>
		<heading>Commands</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the plugin commands that the plugin will respond to, executing the specified script or file along with other configured settings.</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpConfigurationPluginSettings</name>
		<heading>Settings</heading>
		<description>This parameter specifies various plugin settings that can be configured and utilized based on the setting's type.</description>
		<used>Plugin configuration</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionCommandsCommand</name>
		<heading>Command</heading>
		<description>This parameter specifies the command and must begin with the / character.</description>
		<used>Execution commands</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionCommandsHelp</name>
		<heading>Help</heading>
		<description>This parameter specifies the help information for the command. It will be displayed when the ? symbol is sent as an argument to the command.</description>
		<used>Execution commands</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionCommandsExecutionFilePath</name>
		<heading>Execution file path</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the file to be executed when the command is triggered. Since all plugin files are extracted to %infrabot_installation_directory%/plugins/%plugin_guid_number% this directory serves as the root folder for the plugin. The path to the executable file must be specified relative to this directory.&#10;&#10;
Example:
RestartServer.ps1
&#10;
Example 2:
scripts\RestartServer.ps1
&#10;
Example 3:
bin\nodejs.exe
		</description>
		<used>Execution commands</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionCommandsExecutionTimeout</name>
		<heading>Execution timeout (in seconds)</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the execution timeout, specifying the maximum duration a command can run before it is forcibly terminated.</description>
		<used>Execution commands</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionCommandsDefaultErrorMessage</name>
		<heading>Default error message</heading>
		<description>This parameter specifies the default error message that will be displayed if the script execution fails or if the timeout is exceeded.</description>
		<used>Execution commands</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionCommandsType</name>
		<heading>Type</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines execution type. Possible values:&#10;&#10;
AppExecutable - Run executable file.
PSScript - Run PowerShell script.
CSharpScript- Run CSharp cs or csx script file.
		</description>
		<used>Execution commands</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionCommandsExecutionFileArguments</name>
		<heading>Execution file arguments</heading>
		<description>Specifying this parameter is not mandatory, but it is highly recommended if the script requires a fixed number of arguments. When arguments are defined here, before execution, Infrabot will validate the number of provided arguments against the expected ones. If the number of arguments does not match, Infrabot prevents command execution and displays information about the correct command format the user should follow.</description>
		<used>Execution commands</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionFileArgumentsName</name>
		<heading>Name</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the argument name. It is not used in the execution logic, so you can specify any name here. Its primary purpose is to be displayed in help information, providing guidance to the user about the expected argument.</description>
		<used>Execution file arguments</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionFileArgumentsValue</name>
		<heading>Value</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines an example value for the argument. It is not used in the execution logic, so you can specify any value. Its purpose is solely to provide users with a reference example when viewing help information.</description>
		<used>Execution file arguments</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpExecutionFileArgumentsDescription</name>
		<heading>Description</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the description of the argument, which will be displayed to the user as part of the help information, providing guidance on its purpose and usage.</description>
		<used>Execution file arguments</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpPluginSettingsKey</name>
		<heading>Key</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the setting key name, which serves as the identifier for the specific configuration setting within the plugin.</description>
		<used>Plugin settings</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpPluginSettingsValue</name>
		<heading>Value</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines the setting key value, which represents the assigned value for the corresponding setting key name within the plugin's configuration.</description>
		<used>Plugin settings</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpPluginSettingsType</name>
		<heading>Type</heading>
		<description>This parameter defines setting type. Possible values:&#10;&#10;
EnvironmentVariable - Defines a custom environment variable that will be accessible from the script during execution.
Argument - Defines an argument with a value that will be passed to the script during execution. You need to implement logic within the script to read and process the specified argument.
ConfigFile - Defines a setting that will be exported to the tempConfigFile.json file and placed in the %infrabot_installation_directory%/plugins/%plugin_guid_number% directory. You need to implement logic within the script to read and process this file.
		</description>
		<used>Plugin settings</used>
	</item>
	<item>
		<name>HelpPluginSettingsDescription</name>
		<heading>Description</heading>
		<description>This parameter specifies the description of the setting, providing details about its purpose and usage.</description>
		<used>Plugin settings</used>
	</item>
</items>
